[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "How are you, sir?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Well, I've got to get some water.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, let's start with taxes for a moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 49, "question": "And when Romney says he's going to create, well how many million jobs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Twelve million was his last --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "''", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "How can we give to foreign aide?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "You're not the only country that' broken the rule like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "How in debt are we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, you're certainly not as broke as many countries around the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "You don't think Americans have any involvement in any country in the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNPS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Sure we can have involvement if they ask us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Why are we still there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Well, the argument would be to prevent another war in that nation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Isn't that a reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Because our military today --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Would America be safer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Sure, we'd be safe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Without any embassies in any country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "I'm not saying necessarily to get rid of embassies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "Yes, but that wasn't true about the Second World War, was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Probably not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "The reality is sometimes you have to oppress a bad guy, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "At war all the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Why should he get another four years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Well, because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Well, first, Governor, how are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Governor, my question is, if you were to run as independent, completely unaffiliated from any political party whatsoever, do you feel that that would help or hinder your ability to ultimately gain valid access in all 50 states?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "It'll require you the people to do it for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", ",", "CD", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "-- put your butt on the line?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "And the only way that will help, two criteria must happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "But Jesse, will you be running or not, in 2016?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"], "PERSON": ["Jesse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "My question to you is, as a former Navy SEAL, do you agree or disagree with the recent released book by the six-member SEAL Team and -- and the objections of the Pentagon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", ":", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I don't have a problem with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Navy", "Pentagon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "They all sign up, don't they, to not write about their experiences?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Well, he's out now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama"]}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "If he doesn't put in jeopardy anyone, why -- why is our government so up in arms about that he does this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "What we're all agreed on is that the death of Osama bin Laden was a good thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Or from all we're seeing now in the Middle East, all the uprisings, all the kind of reverse Arab Spring, if you like, are you concerned that it may be a hornet nest getting out of control?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "No, because I think a lot of times these uprisings are orchestrated, I believe.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Spring"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Backing in what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "In Libya, in Egypt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "And are we now perhaps seeing the results of not knowing too well who they are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "We're here wanting to give democracy to people who lived, in my opinion, in the stone age.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "They're all about religion and oil and corporations?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Could be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "You're being slightly naive, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I'm not being naive, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "How did they know who did this so quickly like they did Lee Harvey Oswald, how quick they knew Lee Harvey Oswald killed Kennedy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Because the people who did it were identified and we knew who they were.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lee Harvey Oswald", "Lee Harvey Oswald"], "LOCATION": ["Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "How much studying have you actually done of 9/11 other than what the government's told you and what mainstream media has told you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "A lot, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "I know a lot about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":"], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Then why hasn't anyone been brought up for trial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Because --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "If you were the American presidents, with all the jungle drums beating now about Iran, would you take any military action?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Well, first, let me state that Iran has to do this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "How many political offices have you held?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "None.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Hello, governor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "``", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "And how do you think we can fix that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, politics in America, the problem -- the major problem is the Democrats and Republicans, as I explained in my book, \"Democrips and Rebloodicans, No More Games in Government,\" they've created a system based completely on bribery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Mexico"]}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Why it is that Americans -- to me, it seems, so many Americans can not divorce their right to defend themselves with a gun to the apparent right to go and buy 6,000 rounds of ammunition, high powered assault weapons, and go and murder Americans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNPS", ":", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNPS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VB", "CC", "NN", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Well, the best thing I can tell you, Piers, is this: Mexico has strict gun control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "It's inarguable, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "ENTURA: No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "Do we go to the Ford Motor Company and tell them, stop making these automobiles because people get drunk and kill people in cars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "It's a facile argument.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Ford Motor Company"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120917pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "It's a what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "It's a facile.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]